{
    "question": "Apa arti dari andina and andani are very diligent and hardwieking. they get up early in the morning. they always tidy up their bedroms then. they help their parents do the hausework. andina prepares the break fast, and andani sweps the floor and does the laundry, after school, they have extracuticutar aktivitas, andani joins the school choir white andani have same diferent chracters too andina is talkative and outpoken white andani is claim andina talkshow a lot white andani is very queit",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>andina dan andani sangat rajin dan pekerja keras,mereka selalu bangun pagi ,dan mereka merapikan kamar tidur mereka saat itu.mereka [ juga ] membantu orang tua melakukan pekerjaan rumah,andina bersiap sarapan,dan andani menyapu lantai \u00a0dan mencuci pakaian.setelah sekolah,mereka memiliki aktivitas ekstrakuler,andani bergabung dengan paduan suara sekolah [ seterus nya saya tidak tahu :v maaf2 ]</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>kenapa anda tidak mencari di [ mbah ] Google saja :/</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "b-goes-to-her-english-course-w-gucu-6-firman-studies-in-the-ev-278",
            "question": "B. goes to her English course    W gucu\r\n6. Firman. studies in the evening. He does it after dinner everyday.\r\nA. sometimes\r\nB. Rarely\r\nC. always\r\n7. Susi always........... dinner everyday. She likes cooking very much.\r\nA. Make\r\nB. Makes\r\nC. Made\r\n8. My father doesn't............ coffee every morning\r\nA. To drink\r\nB. Drinks\r\nC. Drink\r\nText for no 9-12\r\nIt's nice Sunday morning. Hasan's family are doing separate activities. Mr. and Mrs. Has\r\ngroceries. Rama the oldest son, is playing guitar in the backyard. The twin daughter\r\nbackyard at the same place the youngest daughter Mona. Is drinking a glass of milk.\r\n9. What is Mr. and Mrs. hasan doing?\r\nA. They are on their bike B. They are going to the market C. They are doing\r\n10. What is the twin doing?\r\nA. they are going to the market B. they are playing guitar C. they are readin\r\n11. Who is playing a guitar?\r\nA. Hasan's family\r\nB. Mona's Brother\r\nC. Mona's Sister\r\n12. They are going to the market.\r\nThe underlined word is refers to ...\r\nC. Mr. and Mrs\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "6. C<br>7. A<br>8. C<br>9. B<br>10.  B (kemungkinan besar krna mereka sma\u201d ada di backyard)<br>11. B<br>Idk it\u2019s correct or not, but i hope it will help u^^",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "essays-1-give-2-examples-how-to-offering-help-2-what-is-narativ-308",
            "question": "Essays    1. Give 2 examples how to offering help\r\n2 What is \"Narative Text\"\r\n\r\n3. Write 2 sentences using \"should\"\r\n4. Name 2 examples of \"Quantifiers\"\r\n5. Give 1 sentence of \"Simple Past Tense\"\r\n\r\n\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. a. Would you like some help?</p><p>   b. May i offer you some help?</p><p></p><p>2. A narrative text is a piece of text which tells a story which entertains the reader or listener.</p><p></p><p>3. a. Adam, I&#039;m afraid that you should definitely           see a dentist.</p><p>    b. Robin, I think you should study more.</p><p></p><p>4. a. I saw few people in the program.</p><p>    b. Liam has many friends here.</p><p></p><p>5. He wrote this masterpiece yesterday.</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "this-is-a-wonderful-park-fill-the-blank-with-correct-answer-from-497",
            "question": "This is a wonderful park    Fill the blank with correct answer from the box\r\nA. Lisa : I love cats!\r\nDayu : They're very little. They're babies\r\nB. Edo :.......\r\nUdin: They'.e very friendly and playful\r\nC. Siti :..................... Is it very crowded?\r\nayu : Yes, it is. You'd better go on weekdays\r\nD. Beni:\r\nSiti : She s very kind and polite.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>jawabanya c</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf kalo salah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>B = Edo<u>:How about your classmates at your new school?</u></p><p>C. siti: <u>car free day?!,</u> is it very crowded?</p><p>D. Beni: <u>what do you think about my new girlfriend?</u></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Fill the blank with correct answer from the box:</p><p>Isi bagian yang kosong dengan jawaban yang benar dari kotak.</p><p> aku menjawab apa yang seharusnya di isi </p><p>semoga berguna\u2764\ufe0f</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "rearrange-the-sentences-become-a-good-dialog-a-1-5-3-4-2-243",
            "question": "Rearrange the sentences become a good dialog.\u00a0*    \ufffc\r\n\r\nA. 1-5-3-4-2\r\n\r\nB. 2-5-3-4-1\r\n\r\nC. 2-4-1-5-3\r\n\r\nD. 1-5-2-4-3\r\n\r\nsecepatnya \r\n\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>2-4-1-5-3</p><p></p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p>2. Edo : Have you seen real monkey,Udin? i mean not on tv or in a magazine?</p><p>4. Udin : Yes,I have.</p><p>1. Edo : What are they like?</p><p>5. Udin : They&#039;re very friendly and playful.</p><p>3. Edo : Wow! That&#039;s interesting because as far as i know, not all monkeys are friendly. I want to see one too.</p><p></p><p>hope you find this helpful ^\u2022^</p><p></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "what-is-the-text-about-587",
            "question": "What is the text about\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p></p><p>Teks adalah sebuah wacana lisan dalam bentuk tulisan. Dalam KBBI, teks adalah naskah yang berupa kata asli dari pengarang, kutipan dari kitab suci, bahan tertulis untuk memberikan pelajaran ataupun pidato serta wacana tertulis. </p><p></p><p></p><h2>Semoga Bermanfaat Ya</h2>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "b-what-tara-must-do-before-go-to-riris-house-rearrange-these-s-221",
            "question": "B. What Tara must do before go to Riri's house?    Rearrange these sentences into a good paragraph!\r\n(1) Jack had an accident a few days ago\r\n(2) Jill went to the Hospital to visit him\r\n(3) He is still in the hospital now\r\n4) She is at hospital now\r\n5). He had to go to the hospital\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>halooo teks-nya mana ya? tolong tulis di komentar teksnya, biar saya jawab</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1-5-3-2-4</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>...........</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "3-ahmad-good-night-have-a-nice-dream-amir-good-night-967",
            "question": "3.    Ahmad : Good night, have a nice dream!\r\nAmir : Good night......\r\nA. see you again next time.\r\nB. see you soon.\r\nC. have a nice day.\r\nD. have a nice dream.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>a. good night again next time</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "skins-are-to-apa-artinya-983",
            "question": "Skins are to apa artinya\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>skins are to : kulit untuk apa ?</p><p>hand is to : tangan adalah untuk ? </p><p>foot is to : kaki untuk apa ?</p><p></p><p><strong><em><u>#</u></em></strong><strong><em><u>s</u></em></strong><strong><em><u>e</u></em></strong><strong><em><u>m</u></em></strong><strong><em><u>o</u></em></strong><strong><em><u>gamembantu</u></em></strong></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<h2><u><em><strong>Jawaban:</strong></em></u></h2><h2></h2><h3>ARTINYA : Kulit Untuk Apa</h3><h3></h3><h3></h3><h3></h3><h3></h3><h2><strong><u><em>MAAF KALO SALAH SEMOGA MEMBANTU</em></u></strong></h2><p></p><p></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "sebuah-kotak-dimasukkan-ke-dalam-bejana-yang-berisi-penuh-air-ak-534",
            "question": "Sebuah kotak dimasukkan ke dalam bejana yang berisi penuh air. Akibatnya, sebagian air tumpah. Volume air yang tumpah 600 dm3. Jika percepatan gravitasi g = 10 m/s2, bila massa jenis air 1.000 kg/m3 besar gaya Archimedes pada kotak tersebut adalah \u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>terjemahkan Tujuan Organisasi Budi Utomo adalah Kemajuan Jawa dan Madura Sampai akhirnya tujuan organisasi Budi Utomo diperluas dengan jangkauan yang kelak memungkinkan berdirinya organisasi Budi Utomo. ... Tak lama, tujuan organisasi Budi Utomo berubah menjadi memperoleh kemajuan yang harmonis bagi nusa dan bangsa di Jawa dan Madura dari Melayu~I LOVE YU~</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "read-the-following-text-to-answer-questions-number-15-to-17-last-474",
            "question": "Read the following text to answer questions number 15 to 17. Last month, I sent to Surabaya with my friends for vacation. We went there on a night bus. When we arrived in Lamongan, the bus stopped at a small restaurant for a rest. I got off the bus to get a cup of ginger tea, and my friend drank some cold lemonade. Then I went to the toilet. It tool only a few minutes. When I came out again, the bus was not there, it had gone! My friends were not there too. Feeling shocked and confused. I asked a waiter About the bus. She said the bus departed about five minutes ago. I tried to call my friend on my phone, but the battery as running low. I could not do anything but hope and pray. After several minutes, my wish came true. The bus came back! I got on the bus and walked to my seat. I was so ashamed when everybody on the bus looked at me. I could feel my face turn red. 15. What is the best title of the text above? *     A. My vacation.\r\nB. Vacation with my family.\r\nC. Vacation to Surabaya.\r\nD. Vacation to foreign Country.\r\nLast month I went to Surabaya with my friends for vacation...\" This part belongs to . . . . *\r\nA. Orientation\r\nB. Series of events\r\nC. Reorientation\r\nD. Setting of time and place\r\nThe bus was not there it had gone!\" The word \"it\" in the second paragraph refers to . . . *\r\nA. The writer\r\nB. The bus\r\nC. The waiter\r\nThe cold lemonade\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. A. my vacation</p><p>2. D. Setting of time and place</p><p>3. B. The bus</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p></p><p>semoga membantu :)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}